Guide to the Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015.]
Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015]
- Series IV. Videotapes
  - Subseries IVa. Videotapes transferred from Distributed Learning Services
    - C. U. vs. Brown, basketball, booth, tapes 1-3, February 23, 1990; V-3086 - V-3088; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 37)
    - C. U. vs. Brown, floor cam tape 1, February 23, 1990; V-3089; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 37)
    - C. U. vs. Yale, floor tapes 1-3, February 24, 1990; V-3090 - V-3092; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 37)
    - C. U. vs. basketball practice and loading bus, March 1, 1990; V-3093; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 37)
    - Basketball: Mike Dumont, tapes 1-2, May 1, 1990; V-3094 - V-3095; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 37)
    - C. U. vs. Penn, football, SB-6 T-1 - SB-6 T-10: end zone tapes 1-6, field tapes 1-4, November 19, 1988; V-3096 - V-3105; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 37)
    - C. U. vs. Lafayette, football, SB-10 T-1 - SB-10 T2, field #1-2, October 7, 1989; V-3106 - V-3107; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 37)
    - C. U. vs. Brown, football, SB-10 T-3 - SB-10 T-6: field #1-2, press box #1-2, October 21, 1989; V-3108 - V-3111; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 37)
    - C. U. vs. Bucknell, football, SB-10 T-7 - SB-10 T-10V-3115, press box #1-2, field #1-2, September 23, 1989; V-3112 - V-3115; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 37)
    - C. U. vs. Princeton, football, field #1, V-3116; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 37)
    - C. U. vs. Princeton, football, field #2, top deck #1-3, V-3117 - V-3120; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - C. U. vs. Dartmouth, football, field cam tapes 1-2, top deck tapes 1-2, V-3121 - V-3124; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - C. U. vs. Yale, hockey, tapes 1-3, February 16, 1990; V-3125 - V-3127; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - Laing Kennedy, coach, hockey recruitment, April 23, 1990; V-3128; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - C. S. N. Trant Andison interview, hockey, November 13, 1990; V-3129; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - C. S. N. Schnall audio, hockey, 1991; V-3130; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CHE Volunteer Forum,GI-1 - GI-8, RH-14 - RH-15, tapes 1-8, 14-15, May 1, 1998; V-3131 - V-3140; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: FarmNet interviews, INT116, June 22, 1989; V-3141; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: FarmNet interview & phone, INT117, V-3142; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Heinz Beesdorf at Wegman's, tapes 1-2, January 17, 1991; V-3143 - V-3144; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Mark Wysocki (weather), January 20, 1991; V-3145; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Hazmat - Nutrition Lab, January 21, 1991; V-3146; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Craig Adler - reptiles, tapes 1-2, January 24, 1921; V-3147 - V-3148; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Archives B-Roll, tape 3, January 25, 1991; V-3149; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Harvey Gant, tape 1, January 29, 1991; V-3150; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Bio-degradable, March 18, 1991; V-3151; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Community School of Music & Arts, March 13, 1991; V-3152; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: "Cornell on Top," tape 2, July 26, 1990; V-3153; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Early childhood program, Steve Hamilton, June 3, 1993; V-3154; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Hotel School, HEC '93, April 17, 1993; V-3155; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Johnson Museum exteriors, September 2, 1992; V-3156; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Milking: Waverly Farm, February 13, 1989; V-3157; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Plant Conservatory, March 6, 1991; V-3158; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Statler exteriors, March 6, 1991; V-3159; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - CCR: Wilder Brain Collection, February 26, 1991; V-3160; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - The Partnership with the Marsupial CRC produced by the Boyce Thompson Institute, V-3161; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - Hillary Clinton: PCCW Keynote Address, March 10, 2000; V-3162; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - Hillary Clinton: PCCW Keynote Address, March 10, 2000; DVD-1131; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - Mae Jemison: PCCW Keynote Address, March 11, 2000; V-3163; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - Alumnae Panel, tapes 1-2, March 11, 2000; V-3164 - V-3165; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - Celebrating Nano Bio Technology at Cornell, October 3, 2000; V-3166 - V-3167; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - Nano Symposium, right side of classroom, tapes 1-3, October 3, 2000; V-3168 - V-3170; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - Nano Symposium, left side of classroom, tape 1, October 3, 2000; V-3171; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 38)
    - Nano Symposium, left side of classroom, tapes 2-3, October 3, 2000; V-3172 - V-3173; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Nano Tech, camera 3, tapes 1-5, October 3, 2000; V-3174 - V-3178; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Artists' showcase at Farmers Market, July 23, 2000; V-3179; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Hangar Theatre: Kiddstuff, August 12, 2000; V-3180; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Dracula: back-up of edited silent footage, July 23, 2002; V-3181; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Dracula: show tape, V-3182; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Dracula, October 19, 2002; V-3183 - V-3188; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - A Death in the Family, March 7, 2002; V-3189; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - G & S Bump-Ups, April 28, 2002; V-3190; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - H. M. S. Pinafore, Cornell Savoyards, November 1984; V-3191; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Holiday Inn, V-3192; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Hypergonar: Beneath the Millionaire's Robe, June 7, 2000; V-3193; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Hypergonar: Beneath the Millionaire's Robe, June 6, 2000; V-3194; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Iolanthe, Cornell Savoyards, November 1983; V-3195 - V-3196; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Lady in the Dark, Barnes Hall, September 26, 1998; V-3197 - V-3198; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Mask, V-3199; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - The Mikado, Cornell Savoyards, November 1984 - November 2004; V-3200 - V-3205; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Mikado, V-3206 - V-3207; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Nosferatu, etc., July 14, 2002; V-3208; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Princess Ida, Cornell Savoyards, March 1979; V-3209 - V-3210; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Savoyard Bus & Tour, V-3211; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Utopia, Limited, Cornell Savoyards, April 8, 1984; V-3212 - V-3213; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Yeomen of the Guard, Cornell Savoyards, November 12, 1981; V-3214 - V-3215; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Unidentified (3 tapes), V-3216 - V-3218; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Hypergonar, #1-9, September 2-21, 1999; V-3219 - V-3227; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Hypergonar, #1-6, tr8325d - tr8330d; DAT (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Jimmy, tr8331d; DAT (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Narration, PC & HP, tr8332d; DAT (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Prelims/Reception S---, V-3228; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Reception, Mono 1, V-3229; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Reception, Mono 2, V-3230; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Church Cover, V-3231; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Church Main, V-3232; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Orig. segs, V-3233; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - unidentified, V-3234; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Arts Festival, cued to D. Booth, 1997; V-3235; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - A Death in the Family, January 15, 1996; V-3236; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Silver certificate, September 1999; V-3237; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Dracula (no audio), V-3238; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - M4, M13, M65 (3 reels), F-; Motion picture film (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - The Complete Web Site CD, produced by The Cobb Group, CD-594; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - The Great God Pan, April 1, 2002; CD-595; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - PAN, CD-596; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Mikado (Savoyards), November 21, 2004; CD-597 - CD-599; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Unidentified, CD-600; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Loose sheet with Dracula segments list, CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Accordent Presenter Plus v. 1012, CD-601; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Unidentified, CD-602; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - GloPAC Video Heikyoku: Dragon + Lion Dances, CD-603; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Commencement Helix Project files, CD-604; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Unidentified, CD-605 - CD-610; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - ECE 595 Archives September 2003: 9-8, 9-10, 9-15, 9-22, 9-29, 10-1, CD-611; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Website (Bio G101-104), 05-03-01, ISSO 9660, 5035 Filer/366 Director, CD-612; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - PAR_STREAM.RM 337 ORIG., CD-613; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Large class forum.RM, Michael Camdessus.RM (56K), CD-614; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - --Recover from Graymatter (nr), --Michael Camadessus (DSL).RM, --misc., CD-615; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Audio -- Ulinski, August 11, 2004; CD-616; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - 26*GR, Tuesday Nov. 8th, 1994, ABC, CH9, November 8, 1994; DVD-539; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - 2 RJR*: Tuesday, March 30th, 1999, RBC, March 30, 1999; DVD-540; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Bensuade 2, intro - Q5.d, full NTSC DV captures, unedited, DVD-541; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Bensuade 1, full NTSC DV captures, unedited, DVD-542; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Bensuade 3 errata, last clips, intro - 1A.DC, full NTSC DV captures, unedited, DVD-543; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Unidentified, DVD-544 - DVD-545; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Unidentified, DVD-546; DVD RAM (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Unidentified, ZD-3; Zip drive (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Cyber Tower -Yale - Loehr, tape 2 of 2, July 6, 2004; V-3239; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Bear Rights: A Cyberspace Driver's Aid, V-3240 - V-3241; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Casablanca, V-3242; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Cornell Tradition, V-3243; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Cyber Tower - Shapiro: Music videos, V-3244; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Cyber Tower - Shapiro: transitions, V-3245; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Cyber Tower - Shapiro: Big toy ad, V-3246; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Engineering in the real world, Gus Uht, March 8, 2003; V-3247; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Global Sem Scratch 2, V-3248; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - If Copernicus had a computer, Charles Van Loan, 1996; V-3249; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - ILR: The new workplace, April 1June 18, 1998, building dedication ceremony, April 16-18, 1998; V-3250; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Lederman, CSE conference, April 12, 2002; V-3251; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Project Ezra: Fair, Peter jackson + Jeanne Appling, May 11, 1987; V-3252; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Synergy training presentation: client server version 2.0, V-3253; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Welcome to Cornell: HR new employee orientation video, #2 of 5, V-3254; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Peter Wilhelm interview, June 8, 2002; V-3255; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Unidentified, V-3256 - V-3257; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 39)
    - Unidentified, V-3258 - V-3266; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Colgate, SB-3 T-1 - SB-3 T-3, P/B 1-3, September 24, 1988; V-3267 - V-3269; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Colgate, SB-3 T-4 - SB-3 T-8, Field 1-5, September 24, 1988; V-3270 - V-3274; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Ivy League Trophy, SB-3 T-9, 1988; V-3275; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Ivy League Rings, SB-3 T-10, 1988; V-3276; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Home-Coming, end of game: field camera 1, tape #4, November 5, 1988; V-3277; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Harvard, field camera, tape #1, November 14, 1989; V-3278; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Dartmouth, P/B 1-3, October 28, 1989; V-3279 - V-3281; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Dartmouth, ISO 1-3, October 28, 1989; V-3282 - V-3284; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Dartmouth, Field 1-3, October 28, 1989; V-3285 - V-3287; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Jim Hofher interview, head coach, January 15, 1990; V-3288; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Brown at Cornell, ESPN net feed tapes 1-3, October 27, 1990; V-3289 - V-3291; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Brown at Cornell, side line camera tapes 2-3, October 27, 1990; V-3292 - V-3293; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: C. U. vs. Columbia, Press Box 1-2, November 10, 1990; V-3294 - V-3295; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: C. U. vs. Columbia, Field #2, November 10, 1990; V-3296; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Ed Marinaro, "A Tradition To Cheer About", August 16, 1990; V-3297; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Ed Marinaro footage, 1971; Home Coming footage, 1991, 1971, October 16, 1991; V-3298; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Ramon Watkins Scholar-Athlete, interview, August 30, 1991; V-3299; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Football: Ramon Watkins, October 1, 1991; V-3300; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Hockey: C. U. vs St. Lawrence, November 18, 1989; V-3301; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Hockey: Laing Kennedy interview, cam. 1, cam. 2, November 30, 1989; V-3302 - V-3303; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Hockey: Dave Burke, Field House, December 15, 1991; V-3304; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Hockey: Mike Veley interview, February 17, 1990; V-3305; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 40)
    - Hockey: McCutcheon interview, February 26, 1990; V-3306; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - LaCrosse: Cornell vs. Cortland, March 13, 1990; V-3307; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Women's Soccer: Susan Miller, April 18, 1991; V-3308; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Women's Soccer: Susan Miller, April 25, 1991; V-3309; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Women's Soccer: Susan Miller, October 19, 1991; V-3310; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Moving Families Forward, DVD-546; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - A Day of Remembrance, September 14, 2001; V-1451; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Be Somebody Commons Market, signs on Commons, billboard, Mayers, kids on Commons; OFC115, September 21, 1989; V-3311; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Be Somebody State Fair, 8/30 + 9/4; OFC116, August 30, [1989?]; V-3312; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - State Fair, No. 1, OFC117, V-3313; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Cooperating For Sustainability, W.N.Y. Crop MGMT Assoc. Coop, Dave De Goyler Interview, #9A, #171, February 20, 1997; V-3314; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Cooperating For Sustainability, W.N.Y. Crop MGMT Assoc., De Golyer (PT. II) + Fitch Interview, #9B, #172, February 20, 1997; V-3315; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Cooperating For Sustainability, W.N.Y. Crop MGMT Assoc., Schenk Interview, George Interview, #10B, #173, February 21, 1997; V-3316; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Cooperating For Sustainability, W.N.Y. Crop MGMT Assoc., Dewing Interview, Steward Interview, #11A, #174, February 21, 1997; V-3317; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Cooperating For Sustainability, W.N.Y. Crop MGMT Assoc., Petzen Interview, #11B, #175, February 21, 1997; V-3318; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Cooperating For Sustainability, Anderson Coop, #12A, #176, V-3319; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Cooperating For Sustainability, John Deibec Interview, #12B, #177, V-3320; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Cooperating For Sustainability, Produce + Coops Pickups,#13A, #178, V-3321; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Cooperating For Sustainability, Farm footage NY state, #179, February 28, 1997; V-3322; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Home A Syst, #1A, #180, August 13, 1996; V-3323; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Home A Syst, 1:52:12, #16, #181, August 13, 1996; V-3324; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Home A Syst, Bob's Standup, #2A, #182, August 14, 1996; V-3325; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Home A Syst+, #2B, #183, August 15, 1996; V-3326; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Home A Syst, #3A, #184, September 26, 1996; V-3327; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Henry's Fork (Jan Rown, Emma Atchley), #2A, #228, March 18, 96; V-3328; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Henry's Fork (Emma Atchley), #2B, #229, March 18, 1996; V-3329; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Henry's Fork, Ag Shots, #3A, #230, February 18, 1996; V-3330; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Henry's Fork (AE Shots, Council Meeting), #3B, #231, March 19, 1996; V-3331; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Henry's Fork (council meeting), #4A, #232, March 19, 1996; V-3332; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Henry's Fork (Council Meeting), #4B, #233, March 19, 1996; V-3333; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Henry's Fork, #5A, #234, March 19, 1996; V-3334; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Henry's Fork, 5:36:02, #5B, #235, March 20, 1996; V-3335; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Milwaukee River, #1A, #236, February 6, 1996; V-3336; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Milwaukee River, #1B, #237, February 7, 1996; V-3337; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Milwaukee River, #2A. #238, February 7, 1996; V-3338; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Milwaukee River, #2B, #239, February 7, 1996; V-3339; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Milwaukee River, #3A, #240, February 8, 1996; V-3340; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Milwaukee River, #3B, #241, February 8, 1996; V-3341; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Milwaukee River, #4A, #242, February 8, 1996; V-3342; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Bridge Shots River, Milwaukee Nature Kids Stuff, Tape 00, #243, February 9, 1996; V-3343; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Bruce Baker Interview 1 of 1, Wisc. DNR, #244, March 8, 1996; V-3344; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Bruce Baker Interview 2 of 2, Wisc. DNR, #245, March 8, 1996; V-3345; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - Idaho - Taighee, #6A, #246, March 21, 1996; V-3346; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - NPS - VA, #10A, #247, June 26, 1995; V-3347; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - NPS - VA, #10B, #248, June 28, 1995; V-3348; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - NPS - VA, #11A, #249, June 29, 1995; V-3349; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - NPS - VA, #11b, #250, February 27, 1995; V-3350; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 41)
    - NPS - VA, #12A, #OFC327, #251, June 28, 1995; V-3351; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - NPS - VA, #12B, #252, June 28, 1995; V-3352; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - NPS - VA, #13A, #253, June 28, 1995; V-3353; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Dairy Barn Intgrps, Threes-Tape 2, AG01, August 23; V-3354; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Cutaways Frank Farm, Tape #1, Cows fed by hand and wheelbarrow, farm ext. from across road, AG02, January 22, 1988; V-3355; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Dairy Cattle Tape #2, (Stephenson Rd. Farm), cows standing in paddock, AG03, April 10, 12, 1990; V-3356; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Low input Ag., Manuer load & spread, soil samples, Tape #1, AG04, May 25, 1990; V-3357; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Low input Ag., Tape #2, Toe: at one pt then back, scouting, young corn, fertilizer, planting, AG05, June 5, 1990; V-3358; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - L.I.A. Broadcast Herbicide, Joan Falkenberg, Tape #3, Ridge Till, Spraying, Agent & Farmer in field, AG06, June 21, 1990; V-3359; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - L.I.A., Ridge Tillage in Corn, Tape 4, Falkenberg, AG07, June 26, 1990; V-3360; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - LISA, Corn Rootworm Damage, Tape 5, Low Input 15, AG08, August 23, 1990; V-3361; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - LIA Aurora, Corn (Wed), #6, AG09, August 13, 1990; V-3362; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Corn Harvest, Low input Ag., Tape 1 or 1, #7, Chopping for Feed, AG10, October 17, 1990; V-3363; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - LISA, Soil Lab, Farm/Consultant/IBM, #8, AG11, November 20, 1990; V-3364; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Milking, Tape 3, AG18, October 15, 1986; V-3365; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - T & R Center Dairy Cattle indoor & outdoor pen #5, #2, AG24, April 20, 1988; V-3366; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Dairy Cattle, Wilson Farm (Winter Exts.), #4, #3, AG27, March 17, 1988; V-3367; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Methane Generators Agway, Tully, #2, Hour #3 Cont'd, AG29, October 12, 1988; V-3368; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Methane Generators Meadows, #1, Hour #4, AG30, October 13, 1988; V-3369; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - AG31, V-3370; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Farm Land, Pan's, T.C. 1:00:00 to 1:23:55, AG32, V-3371; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Fistulated Cow, Etienne Belzile, C.S.N., VHS WTE DUB, AG51, November 11, 1992; V-3372; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Apples Geneva Tape 6, AG52, July 13, 1988; V-3373; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Apple Pest, #4, AG53, July 13, 1988; V-3374; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Orchard Pink Session, Tape #3, AG54, V-3375; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Orchard Pink Session, "Apples", Tape #2, AG55, May 12, 1988; V-3376; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Orchard Pink Session, "Apples", Tape #2, AG56, May 12, 1998; V-3377; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Apples Geneva, Tape #5, AG57, July 13, 1988; V-3378; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Hatch #27 Farm #1, New York Farmhouse and crops, mechanical harvest 1" Dub, Hatch #8(2), AG58, September 9, 1986; V-3379; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Hatch Farm #2, New York Farm house and barn/crops, 1"dub, #8(3) Full, AG59, September 9, 1986; V-3380; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Dairy Cattle (Stephenson Rd. Farm) #1, TE: "06" Hours, AG60, April 10, 1990; V-3381; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Whole Farm Planning Cayuga, B-Roll, #4A, AG61, September 1, 1994; V-3382; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Open/Close, Card 1, Promoting Economic Vitality: 1, TEL22, June 1, 1995; V-3383; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Beans Tape #1, #2, 1" Dub, July 28, 1987; V-3384; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - Beans #1, Harvester, Gray Mold - White Moco, Apothecia, Brown Spot, Cover Shots, Gray Mold, August 7, 1987; V-3385; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)
    - CSN1994 Student Music, Cardi music, October 17, 1994, December 8, 1995; V-3386; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 42)